Humpty Dumpty will reach the target area in approximately five hours.
And what about Westcott?
As we expected, he hasn't left his hotel room in Tengu City.
A girl thinks, if only I could be more honest, and she hopes with all her heart that she can find the courage she needs, wishing on every shooting star.
Maybe we went a little too far.
I didn't realize she'd get that upset.
Don't worry, it's really not as bad as you think.
Look, that's her mental state, mood, and happiness.
They've all risen up to much healthier levels.
She's probably not used to being complimented and stuff when she's in her natural form.
Seriously, for someone who's always so desperate to be in the center of the action, girl has zero self-confidence.
You know, now you mention it, Natsumi talked about how nobody ever paid attention to her in her true form.
Sounds to me like a few bad experiences might have really done some damage to her sense of self-worth.
Her beauty isn't the real issue here.
I think in general, Natsumi just needs to feel accepted for who she is.
Those liars, they don't mean any of it.
Haniel, now.
I'll find out the truth.
Toka, Yoshino.
Hi, Koturi.
Are you taking a break, too?
Hey, can I ask you guys a question?
What do you think about that Natsumi girl?
Think.
Meaning?
You know, I mean, how gross can you actually get?
She's so ugly that it's hard not to pity her.
Right?
Koturi, what are you talking about?
This isn't like you.
Excuse me, but I don't think Natsumi's gross or ugly at all.
Here, here.
Wait, what are you even talking about?
You must be blind because that girl is a hot mess.
She's an eyesore.
Hey, what's going on in here?
What's up, Koturi?
You don't seem like yourself today.
It's not me that's off.
They've been saying weird things.
Doubt.
What kind of weird things?
Like that Natsumi is actually pretty
and not the pain in our collective butts that she is?
If you ask me, the only one saying bizarre stuff is you.
Puzzled.
That doesn't sound like something you would say.
Yeah, you really shouldn't be talking about Natsumi like that.
No way, it can't be.
It's a lie.
This means...
Koturi, wait!
Koturi?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
You seem down.
Everything cool?
I'm fine, all right?
Jeez.
Hey, by the way, I had a thought about Natsumi earlier.
Here he comes.
At last I'll get the truth.
I'm wondering if we should let her out of the room for meals.
I've just been thinking about it a lot.
And, well, she's gotta be lonely eating by herself.
But if she got to sit down to eat meals with everyone else,
I think Natsumi might actually warm up to us.
Oh, no.
Hey, what's the matter?
Did I say something to upset you?
Just shut up, you idiot!
Wait!
Koturi!
Whoa, that girl never leaves candy behind.
What's going on with her?
Koturi?
Hey, what's up with you?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Never mind, there's an emergency.
It's Natsumi.
She's escaped from the facility.
Damn it.
I've looked everywhere, but no sign of her.
I doubt she's here, but it's worth a shot.
Natsumi?
Thank goodness, here you are.
You're...
Hello there.
Pardon me for intruding.
Ellen, what are you doing here?
Social call?
After all, what would the great D.E.M. want with little old me?
I came to ask you a question.
Something you want to know?
Indeed.
The spirit you took away with you the other day called Witch.
Where is she?
We need her location.
There's no way in hell I'd tell you that.
Is that so?
Your place is very nice.
I imagine you're all one big happy family together here.
That sweet punch.
Are you prepared to lose them?
I'll ask you one more time.
In return for the continued safety of the other six spirits, tell me where I can find Witch.
Any reaction from Natsumi?
Nothing at point A.
Same goes for point B.
That's not good.
If she's wary of us, she might decide to stay hidden and refuse to show herself again.
Hmm.
This is interesting.
Natsumi?
No, but it's peculiar.
It could be a satellite based on its altitude and trajectory.
That's odd, though.
Why would something like that...
Commander.
There's magical power, but it's faint.
It looks like explosive magic.
Enlarging the image.
Freaking bandersnatch.
Oh, Joy.
Don't tell me.
Yes.
Very well, then.
I'll handle everything here.
Today is your lucky day, Shido Itsuka.
Have you found Natsumi?
Nope.
Had a little trouble.
Shido, I need you to listen.
You're not going to believe this, but please trust me.
In a dozen or so minutes, a satellite will crash into Tengu City.
Wait!
Back up for a second.
Kay, explain.
There's no time now.
It's dangerous to be above ground.
Get yourself to the nearest shelter, okay?
And the others?
Don't worry about them.
The debris won't leave a scratch where they're at, I promise.
Debris?
Yeah.
We're blasting it to smithereens.
Keep searching for Natsumi as long as you possibly can.
But if you can't find her, you have to evacuate before it's too late.
You hear me?
Yeah, I got it.
I'm counting on you, Shido.
Coterie?
What?
Thanks a lot.
That's my life, dork.
I know where to go.
Answer if you can hear me.
Where are you?
Any minute, satellite debris is gonna come crashing down.
It's dangerous to be out here.
Let's get to an underground shelter, okay?
I know where to go.
Just follow me.
Are you listening?
Please!
Not Zumi!
Look, I swear we won't shut you up in a room anymore.
When this is all over, you can go wherever you want, alright?
Okay?
Why go this far from me, especially since the one you're searching for is the disgusting
real me.
I was desperately trying to ruin your life.
I managed to erase your friends and tons of other unmentionable things.
So why is it you care for me so much?
Not Zumi!
Commander, the satellite!
It's time.
Calculate the impact area.
Roger.
Ready?
Let's blow this thing out of the sky.
Not Zumi!
Come on, where are you?
I'm right here!
I'll help you!
Mistleteen!
Fire!
How in the hell?
Yes, that's odd.
I've never heard of anything like that before.
Bandersnatch territory deflecting Mistleteen?
What the?
Incoming from 12 o'clock!
Displaying now!
Isn't that...
Commander?
Well, that's a kink, isn't it?
Kamizuki, I'm leaving you in charge.
Commander.
Now then, shall we get started?
It's time to go to war!
Kamae!
Let's go!
Kamized!
Megid성!
Mechido!
Megidoka!
Mm!
Three!
We're bad!
We're not too many!
Let's go!
Shit!
Watch us!
Let's go!
We're bad!
Mano, you've...
On this?
No! Got near!
Fire!
Ahead!
Target eliminated! Success!
It's a satellite! Another satellite has just appeared!
Kamaeus!
Commander!
Minnie Morin!
Kodori, what are you...
A second one. I'll recover you with Fraxinus, so stay put for now.
In the shelter?
You can't meet... I haven't found her!
Please...
Please save yourself, Shido. You have to forget about me, okay?
Shido, where are you?
Shido!
Hurry, what's going on?
What's happening?
In a little pinch, are we?
What a sad sight, people. Getting all kinds of worked up over nothing.
Agreement. Everyone tried to remain calm.
So wait, is that thing the satellite, then?
You guys, what are you...
Kodori, I'm not seeing Shido anywhere.
Shido is...
Talk to me. What do we do? Just say the word and we'll help out.
Thank you... so much, everyone.
Please go and protect my brother!
I beg you!
It's up to me, then.
Come on, lend me your power!
Sandal Fun!
Here we go.
Chido!
Wait! Toca, what are you doing here?
Simple. Kotori said that you were in a bit of trouble. So we had her send us.
Oh, wow. And Kotori?
They're all busy fighting off the enemy airship.
But don't worry, I think they can handle it on their own just fine.
Man, I honestly thought I'd be a goner.
Good grief, this is really next level.
Outrage, can't they just leave well enough alone?
What we won't let them do as they please.
What are you...
Ellen? How nice to see you.
There's no time for this. You need to get out of here. Those rebels on the board of directors are trying to kill you.
I know all of that.
Then why are you...
Quite simply because I believe they will fail.
What's wrong? Don't you trust me?
Alright, just in case, we'll send her to the scene.
What do you mean?
It can be a little test of sorts.
Gabriel, march!
It's incredible, isn't it?
Man, I knew I liked this song! I'm about to get crazy pumped up!
Affirmative. Very nice assist, by the way.
Look at it!
Toka, help me out! Let's destroy that hunk of junk!
We could do it together!
No, we can't.
Why not? What are you talking about?
I don't know the details, but that satellite has some kind of explosive magic on it.
So unless we destroy it higher in the atmosphere...
Have you forgotten who we are?
We're the Yamai sisters! The Hurricane children! This is what we do!
Solemn pledge. We're gonna blow it away. Ready?
Yes, right! It's all my might!
Yes!
Ouch!
Toka!
Toka, the others!
Congratulations!
Y
Mark, you ok?
Let's go.
Good.
it's okay i know it'll all work out somehow just like it did that other time
it's fine someone will swoop in and help them i know they will
come on show up already someone will they have to
sheena
what the hell
natsumi
look you've got to hurry it up you're trying to destroy that big thing right
yeah
what you waiting for go ahead and smash the dumb thing
but that's really dangerous it's got explosive magic
hanyo
what the hell
there you go surely you can manage it from here right
toka
let's go
was that because of them
kaleidoscope
natsumi
are you sure
what do you think you're doing messing with shido
you should know the only one allowed to do that is me
and don't you forget it
you guys thank you if it had just been me i could never have saved everyone in this city
thank you for everything
natsumi
what is it now are you super disgusted that i changed into a lollipop and hid in your pocket
or are you upset that i didn't come help sooner
i'm glad you're okay
that's weird you don't make sense i literally hid myself away and just watched as you all panicked
and before that i did really terrible things to everyone here too
you're nice i don't get it
why what's your deal
every last one of you
such dummies
hey what's wrong it's okay
i'm so sorry
for doing all those things to you
causing you so much trouble
why none of you have ever been anything but nice to me from the star
which made me happy
but
i was too proud to thank you
i'm so sorry
so thank you really
don't worry about it
besides you seriously saved our lives just now
hey don't cry
remember how i promised you could go anywhere you wanted once this was over
you're one of us now
i hope you'll be my friend
nasumi
darling whatever you're doing is making nasumi cry a lot
what
hey i didn't do it
well i can't leave nasumi in the hands of someone who only makes her upset
so i'll just have to be friends with her too
that's right there's no more teasing nasumi
i'll gladly be your friend too
me too i'd love that
yeah you can be my new kinswoman
agreement and that means we will always protect you
okay wait a minute
why are you all making me out to be the bad guy
i wasn't teasing anyone to begin with
give me a break
good work guys thank you
so um hey could i just ask you do you do you really think that i'm cute
of course i do you're very cute nasumi
um thank you
could you teach me how to do makeup
sure i guess shiori could help you with that
okay
nasumi
about sealing me
how would we do that
um
okay well that's embarrassing
i guess there's not really a choice
Choice
傷だらけのままでしまい込んでた心
君はそっと拾い上げた
繰り返す日々
どうしようもなく紡いた時
ギュッと抱きしめてくれた
ずっとここで
君と二人で夜空流れる
星を見続けたい
君と最後の約束をしよう
世界から私だけ消えてしまっても
気づかれなくていい このままでたい
気づかれたこの気持ち
いつまでも早く
気づかれなくていい
ご視聴ありがとうございました
to play out your deepest, darkest desires
is quite the unique idea, Shido.
True!
Dailing really is a bold one, huh?
What's wrong, Coterie?
Are you serious?
Hey, what's happening, Shido?
It would appear this isn't over yet.
Another bomb is on its way down.
I'm all out of strength.
But I've got to try to stop it.
Now what?
It can't be.
No way.
Origami?
It can't be.